the time of this survey 16
different markers If you have part from one
person then you can have two alleles in each
marker So two peaks you can say i
each marker is
it but in some cases also just an eh is
there are two people, there is one more
placement on one
protective distance
Can you elaborate on how to do it
consider such a notion and
why Yes again then that I should say that
it is unfortunate that these two things
put together, that is, what he tells
know who can LS you can have two different ones
password Yes so a shared phone can
still be one can have a person who has
main control over the phone and
have Notes and so on and protect it
from other users but it can
at the same time shared to be used for as